How is it?
（羅暁(らぎょう)）どうだね？
純潔に包まれる快楽は
The pleasure of being
enveloped by Junketsu?
...I... This is just...
（流子(りゅうこ)）こんな 私…
You and I are the only ones in this
entire world who can feel that pleasure.
（羅暁）その快楽が味わえるのは
この世で私とお前だけ
Enjoy it to the fullest.
存分に享受しなさい
She's right.
Not even I know how it feels.
（縫(ぬい)）そうだよ
僕ですら それは知らない
I'm so envious of you.
うらやましいよ流子ちゃん
The Life Fibers within
Nui's body resist all others.
（羅暁）縫は体の中の
生命戦維(せんい)が反発して—
Even if she wears a Godrobe,
she can't use its powers.
神衣(かむい)を着ても
その能力は引き出せない
Yeah.
（縫）そう だから
僕はグランクチュリエを選んだ
Which is why I chose to
become the Grand Couturier.
I'll just create the ultimate Godrobe myself.
この手で最高の神衣を作り出す
You should be able to
understand how I feel now.
（羅暁）今のお前なら
私の気持ちも よくわかるはずだ
People exist for the sake of clothing.
（流子）人間は服のためにある
Indeed.
（羅暁）そうだ
The beings that stand at the
very apex of life on this planet.
この星の全ての生命の
頂点に立つもの それが生命戦維だ
That is what Life Fibers are.
Hey, Ryuuko.
（縫）ねえねえ流子ちゃん
早く見せてよ
Hurry up and show us.
We want to see you looking your very best.
そのいちばん おしゃれな姿を
Life Fiber Override:
（流子）人衣(じんい)圧倒 神衣純潔
Godrobe Junketsu.
（縫）う〜ん すてき すてき
Amazing!
Lady Ragyou.
（鳳凰丸(ほうおうまる)）羅暁様
皐月(さつき)お嬢様が脱走いたしました
Miss Satsuki managed to escape.
Satsuki did?
（流子）皐月が？
I leave her to you.
（羅暁）お前に任せよう
Gotcha.
（流子）わかった
あっ まだ
お父様の敵を取るつもり？
Do you still want to avenge your father?
Something to feel good about.
景気づけだ
Looks like she can't
suppress her own emotions.
（羅暁）自分の中の情動が
抑えきれぬようだな
She's surprisingly good for
someone so inexperienced.
（縫）思った以上にテクニシャン
まだ経験 浅いくせに
Lady Ryuuko has awakened completely.
（鳳凰丸）流子様
完全に覚醒なさいましたね
Life Fibers are most active
when their host's life is in danger.
（羅暁）生命戦維は
宿主の生命が危険になると—
より活動を活性化させる
Regardless of how deeply
Souchirou sealed them away,
装一郎(そういちろう)がどんなに封印しようと—
subjecting the host to an
intense near-death experience
強烈な死への恐怖を
味わわせれば—
makes it trivially easy to awaken them.
目覚めさせるのはたやすいことだ
Hououmaru.
鳳凰丸 全社員を
ＲＥＶＯＣＳ(リボックス)社に集合させよ
Have all employees gather
at REVOCS headquarters.
I'll head back to the mansion.
私は屋敷に戻る 大詰めだぞ縫
The climax is finally upon us.
う〜 わくわくする
じゃあ 作業 急ぐね
I'm getting goosebumps!
Time to get a move on with my work.
EPISODE 21
INCOMPLETE
unmei no ito wo tachikitta sono saki ni
It all begins when we sever the threads of fate
senobi shiteitanda
I was trying to be someone I'm not
kutsuzure darake no
In a cramped world
semai sekai de
With no breathing room
runway wo aruku
As I walked down my runway
egao no uragawa
I thought I'd concealed it
kakushita tsumori de
Behind the smile that masked my face
dakedo itsumo kimi ni wa
But it doesn't work on you
minukarete shimatte ite
You always see through my facade
konna no wa hajimete de
Nobody's ever unraveled me like this before
tomadou kedo
I don't know what to do
hoka no dare ni mo kikonasenai
Nobody else can pull these outfits off
nandaka wakannai
A somewhat ambiguous fever
atsusa ga mune wo kogasu kara
Threatens to burn our hearts away
unmei no ito taguriyoseta sono saki ni
It all begins once we rein in the threads of fate
ima atarashii yoake ga kuru
A new day will dawn for us
omoi wa kitto hitotsu
We must be one in spirit
（黄長瀬(きながせ)）くっ
Matoi Ryuuko.
（皐月）纏(まとい)流子
お前が妹だったとはな
I never expected you to be my sister.
Don't go all "older sis" on me now.
（流子）
妙に姉貴ぶるんじゃねえぞ
ヘドが出る
Makes me sick.
Oh, you don't have to worry about that.
（皐月）そんなつもりは毛頭ない
I will crush all lapdogs to the Life Fibers
without mercy, no matter who they are.
生命戦維の走狗(そうく)となった者は
誰だろうと容赦なく潰す
（皐月）いくぞ鮮血(せんけつ)
（鮮血）おう
Here we go, Senketsu.
Okay!
Life Fiber Synchronize:
人衣一体 神衣鮮血
Godrobe Senketsu!
GODROBE
SENKETSU
She synchronized with Senketsu
despite having only just put him on?
（美木杉(みきすぎ)）
着たばかりの鮮血で人衣一体するか
さすが皐月お嬢様
That's Lady Satsuki for you.
I can't just sit back
and watch this any longer.
（蟇郡(がまごおり)）もう見ておれん
俺たちも行くぞ！
We should go too!
Let's back Lady Satsuki up!
（猿投山(さなげやま)）皐月様を援護する
（マコ）フン！
（マコ）待ってください！
Wait!
Now is not the time, underachiever!
（蛇崩(じゃくずれ)）
こんなときに何なのよ劣等生！
I have a message from
Lady Satsuki to the Four Devas!
四天王の皆さんに
皐月様から伝言があります
Let's do this,
（流子）いくぜ 皐月！
Satsuki!
Is that Bakuzan?
それは縛斬(ばくざん)か
You're still holding on to
something Mother broke in half?
お母様に一度 砕かれたものを
未練たらしいね
Crying over spilled milk, are we?
未練ではない
執念と言ってもらおうか！
What I'm showing isn't tears. It's tenacity!
It doesn't matter if it's
smashed to bits and pieces.
たとえ粉々に砕かれようと—
So long as a single fragment of it remains,
it will come back to life without a doubt.
僅かでも かけらが残っていれば
必ずよみがえる
我が四天王が
大切に守ってくれていた—
My Four Devas took good care of it for me.
鬼龍院(きりゅういん)皐月と本能字(ほんのうじ)学園の
勝利への執念
Both I, Kiryuuin Satsuki, and Honnouji Academy
share that tenacity and desire to win.
この２本はその象徴だ！
That is what these two blades symbolize!
（流子）いちいち うっせえんだよ
Shut up already!
Run your mouth all you want,
（流子）能書きだけは達者だが
but if you couldn't even manage
to wear Junketsu completely,
純潔も着こなせなかった
てめえじゃ—
you've got no chance of making
full use of that fake either.
そのまがい物の力すら
引き出せねえよ
You think I'm all bark and no bite?
（皐月）この鬼龍院皐月を
口先だけの女と思うか
...Then let me show you...
だったら見せてやる 鮮血閃刃(せんじん)！
Senketsu Blade Flash!
（鮮血）鮮血閃刃！
Senketsu Gale!
鮮血疾風！
（鮮血）鮮血疾風！
Quit ripping me off, bitch!
（流子）てめえ そこまで！
Oh, we're only getting started.
まだまだ これからだ
閃刃疾風！
Blade Gale!
Interesting.
（鮮血）面白い
Blade Gale!
閃刃疾風！
Okay.
よーし 今日は
これぐらいでいいかな
That should do it for today.
フン！ 少しはやるな
Guess you're not completely inept.
Ryuuko.
（鮮血）流子
そんな服は脱いで 私を着てくれ
Take that outfit off
and wear me instead!
You've gotta be kidding me.
（流子）冗談じゃねえ
そんな醜い姿に二度となれるか
I never want to look that ugly again.
I'm ugly?
（鮮血）私が醜い？ 本気か流子
Do you really mean that?
Yeah.
ああ そんな服を着てんだか
着てないんだか わからねえ姿
That half-assed getup where you
can't even tell if they're clothed or not?
It's the very definition of ugly.
醜い以外の何物でもねえ
By making the least possible
amount of skin contact,
（皐月）
生命戦維のとりこになる愚を
犯さぬために—
one can draw out the Life Fibers' powers
without falling under their influence.
最低限の接触面で
生命戦維の力を引き出す
GODROBE
SENKETSU
That is the purpose of the
Life Fiber Synchronize form.
それが人衣一体形態だ
むしろ人類の知恵と言ってもらおう
SENKETSU
If anything, it's proof of human ingenuity.
"Ingenuity", my ass.
何が知恵だ
ただ おびえてるだけじゃねえか
It's just fear.
You want the power of clothing,
服の力は欲しい
でも心を乗っ取られるのは嫌だ
but you're afraid of
losing control of your mind.
That outfit symbolizes your
unwillingness to go all the way.
そういう中途半端な気持ちの象徴が
その格好だ
It's completely and utterly shameful.
つくづくみっともねえよ！
That's not true.
（鮮血）それは違う
Whenever you activated
Life Fiber Synchronize mode,
お前が人衣一体になったとき—
you were wearing me,
and I was being worn by you.
ちゃんと流子は私を着て
私は流子に着られていた
Right now, you're just
being worn by Junketsu.
（皐月）今の貴様は
純潔に着られているにすぎない
And what's wrong with that?
（流子）それの何が悪い
純潔に着られた快感 たまらねえよ
The pleasure of being worn
by Junketsu is out of this world!
People are born to be worn by Life Fibers.
人間は生命戦維に着られるために
生まれたんだ
Adorning them should be
their greatest happiness in life.
彼らによく着てもらうのが
いちばんの幸福なんだよ
That is a slave's happiness!
それは奴隷の幸福だ
If you don't like it,
then you'd better die.
それが嫌なら死ぬんだな
"Submit or die".
服従か死か いかにも
てめえが好きそうな言葉じゃないか
Sounds like your kind of phrase, eh,
え！ 鬼龍院皐月！
Kiryuuin Satsuki?!
（皐月）あっ… 鮮血閃刃
Senketsu Blade Flash!
（鮮血）鮮血閃刃！
（流子）フン！
（鮮血）うっ
（皐月）ひるむな！
Falter not!
I see, I see.
なるほど そういうことか
You aren't truly wearing
that Godrobe, are you?
やっぱりてめえは
その神衣 着こなしてねえな
（皐月）なっ… 鮮血疾風！
Senketsu Gale!
Too slow.
（流子）遅(おせ)え
（鮮血）ぐはっ
（皐月）くっ 閃刃疾風！
Blade Gale!
Still too slow!
（流子）それも 遅え！
（鮮血）ぐわー
Lady Satsuki!
（蟇郡･猿投山）皐月様！
（蛇崩）皐月ちゃん！
何やってんだ
What is wrong with you?!
What's the matter?
（流子）どうしたどうした
反撃できねえのか？
Can't attack me?
You can't, can you?
できねえよな
てめえの動きは見切られてるからな
I can see through your
every move, after all!
（皐月）ぐはっ
Take that!
（流子）おらー！
"Life Fiber Synchronize", my ass.
何が人衣一体だ てめえと鮮血は
何一つ つながっちゃいねえ
You and Senketsu aren't
on the same page at all.
お前が口で指示して
鮮血は鮮血の力で攻撃する
All you're doing is ordering
Senketsu to attack using his powers.
That's why your teamwork's all wonky.
だから変形に一瞬のズレが出来る
You're the one who's just
being worn by her Godrobe.
てめえこそ神衣に
着られてるだけじゃねえか
You haven't improved
since wearing Junketsu at all!
純潔のときから
何一つ進歩しちゃいねえ！
（流子）フン！
（皐月）ぐあっ
I've had it up to here with your posturing.
（流子）まったく てめえの
はったりにはうんざりだぜ
What's wrong?
どうしたどうした
いつものように人を見下ろさねえか
Hard to look down on people
from the dirt, ain't it?
If you can't stand by yourself,
maybe I should lend a hand.
自分で立てねえんなら
あたしが立たせてやろうか
Does this calm you down, "Lady Satsuki"?
これで落ち着くか？
え 皐月お嬢様
But you know what?
You've got nothing at your feet.
だが てめえの足元には
何にもねえよ
てめえは砂の城に立ってた
哀れなお姫様だ
You're a pathetic princess who
stands atop a mere sandcastle.
One wave is all it takes to
wash your kingdom away.
波が来りゃ
たちまちその城は崩れ去る
Stop it, Ryuuko.
（鮮血）やめろ流子
（流子）あ？
Yes, my words don't reach Satsuki.
（鮮血）確かに皐月には
私の言葉は伝わらない
And yes, this Life Fiber Synchronize
is but a stopgap measure.
人衣一体も かりそめのものだ
だが心はつながっている
However, our hearts are as one.
We stand together in our desire
to bring you back to your senses.
お前を正気に戻すという
思いは１つだ
Shut the hell up.
黙れ
Do you have any idea how much stress
Satsuki's placing on her body to let me fight?
（鮮血）私に戦わせるために—
どれだけの負荷が
皐月の肉体にかかっていると思う
No other human could pull that off.
そんなこと ほかの人間では無理だ
鬼龍院皐月でなければな
Only Kiryuuin Satsuki can!
So what?
だからどうした
負け犬に変わりはねえ！
She's still a loser!
You sure are annoying
for a scrap of clothing.
いちいちグチャグチャ
うるせえんだよ ぼろ布が
I'll chop you to pieces along with Satsuki!
皐月ごと ぶった斬って…
Don't you dare insult Satsuki!
皐月ちゃんをバカにするな！
Her sandcastle is made of steel!
皐月ちゃんの砂の城は
鋼の砂の城なの！
It won't fall apart that easily!
簡単に崩れ去ったりしないの！
Stay out of this!
（流子）邪魔くせえ！
（猿投山）てーい！
Don't you realize what
Lady Satsuki wants?
皐月様の真意も読めぬとは
貴様の目は節穴だ
You must have holes for eyes!
（流子）
ただの人間がうざいんだよ
そんなナイフで何ができる！
You're just a human. Spare me.
What can you do with those paltry knives?
（猿投山）フン！
"What", you ask?
（犬牟田(いぬむた)）何って
射程内への誘導ができるんだね
Well, he can lure you into firing range.
Did you really think
that'd work on Junketsu?
そんなもの純潔に効くと思ったか
（流子）うっ
（蟇郡）だが 近寄る隙は作れた
No, but it did give me
the chance to close in on you.
What?
（流子）何！
I'm going to pull you out from Junketsu!
（蟇郡）引き抜いてやるよ
純潔から貴様を！
Damn it, Satsuki!
皐月 てめえ
最初から これが狙いで！
Was this your plan all along?
Precisely!
そのとおりだ
私と鮮血では今のお前に勝てない
Senketsu and I can't
beat you as you are now.
But entrusting the Four Devas with
the finishing blow gave us a chance!
だが四天王に勝機を託せば
可能性はある
All right! Just as planned!
（犬牟田）よし 作戦どおりだ
Still, I can't believe Lady Satsuki suggested
a combination attack with the Four Devas.
しかし あの皐月様が
四天王との連携作戦を提案するとは
And most of all, I can't believe Mankanshoku
accurately relayed that complicated message.
何より驚いたのは—
満艦飾(まんかんしょく)君がこの複雑な伝言を
ちゃんと伝えられたことだ
Lady Satsuki wrote it down
on my hands for me!
皐月様が手に書いてくれました！
Trust her to be thoroughly prepared.
さすが用意周到
Who would've thought
you'd play the decoy yourself?
まさか てめえ自身が
おとりになるとはな
I'll do whatever it takes to win.
勝つためには手段は選ばない
Did you forget that's how I do things?
それが私のやり方だということを
忘れたか
Now, I'll tear you away from Junketsu
今 純潔から引き剥がして
正気に戻してやるぞ
and bring you back to your senses!
くっ なぜ纏を分離できない
Why can't I separate Matoi?!
Run, Gamagoori!
（皐月）逃げろ 蟇郡！
（蟇郡）あっ
Harime Nui!
針目(はりめ)縫
Damn you!
てめえ！
Useless, useless, useless.
（縫）無駄よ 無駄無駄
ホント人間て
無駄なことばっかりやるよね
Really, humans waste
so much time on pointless things.
絶対 僕にそんな弾は当たらないし
Those shots will never hit me.
（黄長瀬）ぐわー
And Ryuuko can never take Junketsu off!
絶対 流子ちゃんは純潔を脱げない
（黄長瀬）ぐはっ
Why is that?
なぜだ
I mean, I sewed the Life Fibers
within her body and Junketsu's together.
だって 流子ちゃんの体の中の
生命戦維と—
純潔の生命戦維を
しっかり結んでるんだもん
If you try to forcefully take it off,
they'll get ripped apart, and she'll die.
無理に脱がそうとしたら
ちぎれてショックで死んじゃうよ
What?!
（鮮血）何！
（皐月）貴様！
How dare you!
She sewed the Godrobe onto her body?!
（美木杉）
神衣を体に縫い付けてるのか
That's awful!
What kind of punishment is that?
ひどい！ 何の罰ゲームよ えいっ
ん〜！ トオッ！
I'm Mankanshoku Mako,
満艦飾マコ 参る！
leaping into action!
We successfully completed the acquisition of
every sewing factory in China and India the other day.
（鳳凰丸）先日 中国とインドの
縫製工場の買収に成功した結果—
As a result, REVOCS now holds a
100% share of the world's market.
今やＲＥＶＯＣＳ社の世界シェアは
100パーセントになりました
Humans all across the globe are wearing
our clothing in one way or another.
全世界の人間が何らかの形で—
我が社の製品を
身につけているということです
Congratulations!
（モニター:羅暁）おめでとう諸君
生命戦維は全人類に行き渡った
Life Fibers have spread
through all of mankind.
Now there's just one last task
for you all to complete.
（モニター:羅暁）諸君たちにも
最後の働きをしてもらう
The original Life Fiber,
which touched down on planet Earth,
（羅暁）
地球にたどりつき 服を与え—
stimulated mankind's evolution
by providing it with clothing
人類を進化させた
原初(げんしょ)生命戦維は—
and then went into a dormant state
until humanity advanced sufficiently.
人類が相応の進化を遂げるまで
眠りについた
Our job as the Kiryuuin family
was to protect it until then.
それを守るのが
我が鬼龍院一族の務めだった
Only one Kiryuuin head
would ever see it reawaken.
その覚醒に立ち会える当主は
ただ１人
それが私だったことを
時に感謝するよ
I thank Father Time for
choosing me as that person.
Now I can witness this
amazing event with my own eyes.
今から起こるすばらしい出来事を
この目で見られるのだからな
（黒井戸(くろいど)）おお〜 これは…
What's happening?
This world shall belong to the Life Fibers.
（羅暁）この星が
生命戦維のものとなる—
This is the genesis of the Cocoon Planet!
繭星(まゆぼし)降誕の始まりだ
GENESIS OF THE
COCOON PLANET
Congratulations, milady.
（黒井戸）おめでとうございます
Kuroido.
黒井戸 お前たちも加わりたいか？
Do you and the others
wish to take part as well?
May we?
（黒井戸）よろしいのですか？
（羅暁）ああ
Indeed.
Thank you very much!
（黒井戸）
ありがとうございます
ああっ…
おお すばらしい
心地いいですぞ
How wonderful!
This is most pleasant,
Lady Ragyou!
羅暁様！
Let us go to where it all begins.
行きましょう 始まりの地へ
（流子）おら！
Eat this!
（流子）食らえ！
（流子）おらあ！
（鮮血）ぐわっ
Senketsu!
鮮血！
（流子）とどめだ！
This is the end!
Stop!
（マコ）ダメー！
（マコ）んぬぬ… フン！
I can understand
why you're mad, Ryuuko.
流子ちゃんが怒る気持ちはわかる
確かにその服が脱げなかったら—
Yeah, if you can't take those clothes off,
お風呂に入ってても体洗えないし
デートのときも おめかしできない
you can't wash yourself
even if you take a bath,
and you can't dress up
when you have to go on a date!
But that doesn't mean
you should go this crazy!
Objection
でも だからといって
こんなに暴れちゃダメだよ
What the hell are you talking about?
（流子）お前は何を言っている
逃げろ 満艦飾
今の纏はいつものあいつじゃない
Run away, Mankanshoku!
Matoi's not her usual self right now!
Ryuuko is always herself!
（マコ）流子ちゃんは
いつだって流子ちゃんです
Even if she's got Life Fibers in her body,
生命戦維が体に入ってても
人間じゃないって怒ってても—
or if she's mad that she's not human,
Ryuuko's still herself!
それでも流子ちゃんは
流子ちゃんじゃないですか
Objection
And Senketsu is her best outfit!
そして鮮血ちゃんは
やっぱり流子ちゃんの一張羅です！
She's such a nuisance.
あの子 邪魔ね
...Mako...
（鮮血）マコ
Mako!
マコ〜！
...Whoa, could this be...?
おお！ これはまた
I took some of your blood.
（鮮血）お前の血をもらっている
頼むから貧血だけは起こすなよ
Please, just don't get anemic!
Girls who try to punch above their weight and wear
outfits that don't suit them are what I hate most.
似合わない服着て
頑張ってる女って いちばん嫌い
みっともなくて虫ずが走る
They're so pathetic I could hurl.
（黄長瀬）うりゃ
I told you it was useless!
（縫）だから無駄だって
（皐月）てーい
You still don't get it?
まだわかんないの？
A mere human couldn't possibly beat me.
ただの人間が勝てるわけないのに
Be that as it may, the blade
within my heart still stands firm.
だが 心の刃(やいば)は折れてはいない
Sheesh, how persistent.
まったく しつこいね
Ryuuko belongs to Lady Ragyou.
流子ちゃんは
羅暁様のものだっていうのに
I wonder about that.
（皐月）それは どうかな
（縫）あなたも
流子ちゃんの情に訴えるの？
Are you going to appeal to her emotions too?
That's just useless.
そんなことをしても無駄無駄
皐月ちゃんも甘くなったね
How naïve you've gotten, Satsuki.
（皐月）
私が逆転の可能性を信じているのは
貴様のおかげだよ
You're the reason I believe there's
still a chance to turn this around.
I am?
（縫）僕の？
（皐月）
ああそうだ　纏流子が完全に
貴様たちの味方になったのなら—
Indeed.
If Matoi Ryuuko is indeed
completely on your side,
then why don't you let her
have that Sword Scissor?
なぜ その片太刀バサミを渡さない
Those scissors are the last weapon
that can oppose the Life Fibers.
（皐月）そのハサミは
生命戦維に対抗しうる最後の武器
You're holding on to one half of it
because you're still a touch anxious.
それをいまだ手にしているのは—
貴様に一抹の不安が
残っているからだ
That very anxiety is our path to victory!
その不安にこそ我々の勝機はある
The look on your face has convinced me.
その動揺で ますます確信した
我々は勝つ！
We will prevail!
Leave her to us!
ここは俺たちが！
You take care of Matoi!
（蟇郡）皐月様は纏を
（蛇崩）私たちの希望はあなたよ
You're our only hope!
頼んだぞ
I'm counting on you!
Ryuuko!
流子ちゃん
その子 鮮血ごとやっちゃって！
Kill that girl along with Senketsu!
That's what Lady Ragyou wants.
羅暁様もそれを望んでるわよ
Show these simpletons talking about
hope just how dark reality can be!
希望がどうとか言ってる
このスイートたちに—
真っ黒な現実を教えてやって
Gotcha.
わかった
Outta my way.
（流子）どけ
（鮮血）やめろ流子
Knock it off, Ryuuko!
So you're going to protect that girl?
（流子）その女を守るか
（鮮血）マコも守る
だが守りたいのはお前もだ 流子
Yes, I will.
But I also want to protect you, Ryuuko!
Me?
（流子）私？
That's right.
（鮮血）ああそうだ
If you kill Mako right here and now,
that will hurt you most of all!
今ここでマコを殺したら
いちばん傷つくのはお前だ
So I won't let you, no matter what!
だから絶対に
マコに手は出させない
Say what?
（流子）何
It's all because you're so selfish, Ryuuko!
（マコ）流子ちゃんが
わがままばっかり言うから—
Now Senketsu's been worn by me instead!
鮮血ちゃん私に着られちゃったよ
こんなのおかしいよ
This just isn't right!
I'm sure you can take that outfit off.
流子ちゃんなら その服脱げるよ
だから早く着替えようよ
So hurry up and change!
Shut up already, will ya?!
（流子）キンキンうるせえんだよ！
（皐月）フンッ！
Now, Mankanshoku!
今だ 満艦飾
この傷口に鮮血を突っ込め！
Stick Senketsu into this wound!
What?!
Senketsu!
鮮血！ 純潔と結び付いた
纏の生命戦維
Use your powers to untangle
Matoi's and Junketsu's Life Fibers!
お前の力で振りほどけ
All right!
（鮮血）おう
（マコ）わかりました
Understood!
Here I come, Ryuuko!
（鮮血）流子 いくぞー！
I'm going to force you to change!
力ずくで着られてやる！
It's high time you learned how
powerful one's best outfit can be!
一張羅の力 思い知れ〜
Ryuuko!
（マコ）流子ちゃん 迎えに来たよ
（鮮血）流子！
We've come for you!
Ryuuko!
I'll kill anyone who dares
destroy my happiness.
私の幸せを壊すヤツは殺す
How can you call this happiness?
こんなの幸せでも何でもないよ
こんなの流子ちゃんじゃないよ！
This isn't like you at all!
Shut up.
（流子）黙れ
Come to your senses, Ryuuko!
（鮮血）目を覚ませ流子
（流子）やかましい
Shut the hell up!
You stupid, foolish, fool!
Fine. Kill me!
いいよ 殺しなさいよ
If you insist on staying
cooped up in here forever,
どうしてもこんなとこで
閉じこもってたいなら—
私 殺して
流子ちゃんやめちゃえ！
kill me, and quit being Ryuuko!
Ryuuko!
（マコ）流子ちゃーん
（鮮血）流子！
ハァ ハァ
纏…
...Matoi...
Oh dear.
（縫）あーらら
説得も失敗だったみたいね
Looks like your plan to
win her over ended in failure.
Come on, Ryuuko.
じゃ 流子ちゃん
一気にこの船 沈めちゃおうか
...Let's send this ship...
to Davy Jones' locker!
What?
何？
Quit doing as you damn well please!
いつまでも
勝手やってんじゃねえ！
No way!
まさか…
How dare you make me wear this outfit?!
（流子）よくも こんな服
押しつけやがったな！
Ryuuko!
（マコ）流子ちゃん
（鮮血）流子！
Ryuuko!
Screw it. I've had enough!
（流子）だが もうごめんだ
Ryuuko!
流子君
I've had enough!
（流子）もう ごめんだ！
Matoi!
Transfer student!
（猿投山･蟇郡）纏！
（蛇崩）転校生
I've had enough!
（流子）もう ごめんだ！
Stop it, Matoi!
よせ 纏
無理に引き剥がすと死ぬぞ！
You'll die if you try to
take it off by force!
Dying is fine by me!
（流子）死んでいいんだよ！
I have to take this thing off,
even if it costs me my life!
死んでも脱がなきゃ
いけねえんだよ！
...Or else...
でなきゃ…
また鮮血は着られないだろうが！
I won't be able to wear Senketsu again!
kurikaesu mainichi ga
My monotonous everyday life
totsuzen iro wo kaeru
Took on a new hue
sonna koto dokka nozonde itanda kedo ne
A part of me always wished for that to happen
iza to naru to
But when it actually did
okubyoumono deshita
I was too scared to act
himitsu ne
That's a secret, okay?
hitori furuete
Trembling alone
soshite kimi ni aitakute
I miss you so much
zutto mikata da yo nante ieta nara
If only I could tell you that I'll always be on your side
muteki
We could be invincible
sou sa tobitatsu toki wa futari de
When we take flight, we'll do so together
tachimukai
We'll make a stand
kakaekirenai okubyou ni
I want to keep smiling
tsuppattatte waratte itai
Even when my cowardice freezes me in place
hitori kiri zutsu ga awasatte
Every little thing will come together
ookina chikara ni naru yo
To give us great strength
ima nee kanjita
That's how I feel right now
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
（鮮血）誰かが言った
Someone once said that
each person's life is a tapestry.
“人の一生は
一枚のタペストリー”だと
A TAPESTRY
決して交わらない２枚のつづれ織が
１つに重なるときが来た
The time has come for two woven tapestries
that can never intermingle to overlap and become one,
WOVEN
OVERLAP
そのきっかけはコロッケ？
their mutual understanding
sparked by... croquettes?!
SPARKED
CROQUETTES?!
次回 キルラキル
「唇よ、熱く君を語れ」
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"Tell Me How You Feel".
EPISODE 22
TELL ME HOW YOU FEEL